<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>News API</title><link>https://newsapi.org/</link><description>RSS feed based on news api response</description><item><title>US deal with Russia on Syria will save 'tremendous numbers of lives': Trump</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-11/trump-says-us-deal-with-russia-on-syria-will-save-many-lives/9141522</link><description>Donald Trump says an agreement with Russian President Vladimir Putin on Syria would save many lives.</description><pubDate>None</pubDate></item><item><title>Ellyse Perry stars for Australia with record knock against England</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-11/ellyse-perry-stars-for-australia-in-womens-ashes-test/9141612</link><description>Ellyse Perry breaks the Australian women's Test record for the highest score, smashing an unbeaten 213 against England in their day-night Women's Ashes encounter at North Sydney Oval.</description><pubDate>None</pubDate></item><item><title>Queensland Premier rubbishes One Nation's claims schoolchildren taught masturbation</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-11/annastacia-palaszczuk-rubbishes-one-nations-safe-schools-claim/9141520</link><description>Queensland Premier Annastacia Palaszczuk slaps down One Nation's claims that teachers are showing children sex tricks in the classroom as untrue.</description><pubDate>None</pubDate></item><item><title>John Alexander resigns amid deepening citizenship crisis for Government</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-11/john-alexander-to-resign-amid-dual-citizenship-concerns/9138814</link><description>Federal Liberal MP John Alexander has become the latest victim of the citizenship scandal, resigning after reaching the conclusion he can not be certain he is not a dual citizen.</description><pubDate>None</pubDate></item><item><title>Trawler Dianne survivor Ruben McDornan speaks of heartbreak over lost mates</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-11/ruben-mcdornan-facebook-post-tribute-trawler-sinking-qld/9141064</link><description>The sole survivor of a trawler that capsized off the Queensland coast opens up publicly for the first time, posting an emotional tribute to his six lost crewmates on social media.</description><pubDate>None</pubDate></item><item><title>Tonga upsets New Zealand in Rugby League World Cup boilover</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-11/tonga-beats-new-zealand-in-rugby-league-world-cup/9141468</link><description>Tonga creates Rugby League World Cup history with a stunning 28-22 victory over giants New Zealand.</description><pubDate>None</pubDate></item><item><title>'Fundamental agreement' reached on rebadged TPP deal</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-11/trans-pacific-partnership-fundamental-deal-reached/9141384</link><description>Eleven Pacific Rim countries reach agreement on continuing with a free trade pact after the US abandons it.</description><pubDate>None</pubDate></item><item><title>One Nation, Jacqui Lambie eye off Tasmanian election</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-11/pauline-hanson-and-jacqui-lambie-parties-register-in-tasmania/9141378</link><description>Pauline Hanson and Jacqui Lambie could run candidates in the next Tasmanian election, as incumbents warn against negative campaigning.</description><pubDate>None</pubDate></item><item><title>Three lawyers charged in probe into suspected criminal activity in Qld</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-11/three-lawyers-charged-in-ccc-probe/9141254</link><description>Three Brisbane lawyers are charged with aggravated fraud after a joint Queensland police and CCC investigation into suspected criminal activity within elements of the legal profession.</description><pubDate>None</pubDate></item><item><title>Despite the 0-0, it finally clicks for Ange's Socceroos in their best away performance</title><link>http://www.abc.net.au/news/2017-11-11/socceroos-best-away-performance-against-honduras/9141088</link><description>It was frustrating, and there's still some work to do, but the Socceroos produce arguably their best performance on the road in some time in the 0-0 first-leg draw with Honduras.</description><pubDate>None</pubDate></item></channel></rss>